PIYUSH KHANDELWAL

+919672541707 | +447880037276 piyushkhandelwal1997@gmail.com LinkedIn

Mumbai, India / Luton, UK

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A strategic marketing graduate with strong work and academic experience in sales and key account management. I aim to contribute well towards any organisation with both my engineering and marketing aptitude to help scale revenue and enhance branding. My experience varies from working with small scale start-ups to large scale MNCs with strong focus in advertising, business development and key account management of large accounts.

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- Certified by Market Research Society, UK in market research with Merit
- Awarded a company sponsored trip to the Maldives in November'2019 for strengthening core business and supply chain
- Headed Sri-Lanka business development and market research at Flynote to jump start a fresh destination in 2 weeks
- Generated over 100,000 USD worth of revenue month on month

EDUCATION

MSc Strategic Marketing, Cranfield School of Management, Cranfield, UK

Sept 2021 - Sept -2022

Key Modules: Big Data Insights & Analytics, Strategic Marketing & Planning, Consumer Behaviour, Managing Brands, Digital & Social Media Marketing, Retail and Omnichannel Management

Highlights: Marketing Consultancy Project with "Birdseye UK"; Sales and Key Account Management with "Jacobs Engineering Group, USA", Branding with "MIND BLMK" (Non-Profit)

B.Tech Information Technology, Manipal University, Jaipur, India

Aug 2015 - Aug 2019

Highlights: Member of Organizing Committee for various fests; Coverage Photographer for key events throughout the years

SKILLS

- **Technical Skills:** JMP (Statistical Analysis), NVivo (Qualitative Data Analysis), LinkedIn Sales Navigator, Salesforce, SugarCRM, SAS (Statistical Analysis)
- Management Skills: Microsoft Office, Key Account Management (Large Accounts Ecosystem), Sales & Business Development, Advertising Account Management, A/B Testing, Brand Management & Retailing
- Language Competence: TOEFL 101/120, CEFR C1 Equivalent

CAREER HISTORY

Henkel Ltd, Hemel Hempstead, United Kingdom

Sept 2022 - Nov 2022 & Jan 23 - Present

Henkel is a leading solution provider for adhesives, sealants and functional coatings for consumers, craftsmen and industrial applications. It has a market cap of nearly 30 Billion USD with over 52000 employees globally in 79 countries.

Digital Key Accounts Sales Graduate

- Took responsibilities of an Account Based Marketing Social Selling Manager as a graduate for large accounts ecosystem
- Mapped few of the largest accounts of Henkel's Datacom and Telecom SBUs on LinkedIn Sales Navigator
- Be the pivotal digital right hand of Global Key Account Managers handing clients like Cisco, Nokia and Ericsson.
- Analyse key stakeholder networks of Global Key Accounts and cover untapped areas for marketing activation.

Hennes & Mauritz H&M, Milton Keynes, United Kingdom

Nov 2021 – Aug 2022

Hennes & Mauritz AB is a Swedish multinational clothing company head-quartered in Stockholm. It is known for its fast-fashion clothing for men, women, teenagers, and children.

Sales Advisor

- · Performed in-store sales advisory and operations within several apparel departments
- Achieved a membership score of more than 60% throughout with 40% being store's average

Media.net, Mumbai, India

Aug 2020 - Sept 2021

Media.net is a leading global advertising company with one of the most comprehensive portfolios of advertising technology in the industry across search, native, display, mobile, local, products and video.

Associate - Publisher Development

- Managed onboarding for over 400 potential accounts under Activation Vertical (US & UK Based Clients)
- Leading activation vertical with more than 15% conversion rate of incoming leads
- Supervised Account management for over 150 accounts in a span of 6 months

Upgrad, Mumbai, India

Mar 2020 – June 2020

Upgrad is an online higher education platform providing rigorous industry-relevant programs designed and delivered in collaboration with world-class faculty and industry. Merging the latest technology, pedagogy, and services.

Sales Consultant (Admissions Counsellor)

- Accomplished more than 4000 USD sales in first month of joining
- Bootstrapped online MBA vertical sales with recognisable success rate of over 12% conversion

Flynote, Bengaluru, India

Jan 2019 – Feb 2020

Flynote is a curated marketplace for consumers and agents. It connects consumers with expert agents who design itineraries and hunt best deals on flights, hotels, cars among others.

Sales Team Lead (Experts Success Manager)

- Applied performance data to evaluate and improve operations, target current business conditions, and forecast needs.
- Accomplished overall sales growth of 15% quarter on quarter
- Managed a sales team of more than 10-12 associates for a period of 7 months
- Initiated and launched Sri-Lanka as a new destination within 14 days of end to end process